cinepolisindia.com 2019-03-03

# Introduction

Introduction
Your privacy is important to www.cinepolisindia.com. We recognize that when
you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a
responsible manner. This information helps us improve your movie going
experience with better content, services and opportunities. This policy tells you
about the information gathering and dissemination that we conduct. As we
continue to grow, this policy may change, so please check back periodically for
updates.
The Information we Collect
   • We ask our users to register when they use
       the www.cinepolisindia.com site and services (collectively, the "Service").
       Through our online registration process, we collect a variety of
       information about the user, which may include, among other things, name
       of the person registering, location, gender, phone number, email address,
       user name and password. www.cinepolisindia.com may also request and
       collect other information from time to time.
   • We automatically track information related to use of the Service. This
       information may include, among other things, URL tracking information,
       what browser the user is using, the user's IP address, pages and ads
       viewed by a user and selections or other actions taken on the Service. We
       may track usage through cookies. A cookie is a small data file written to a
       user's hard drive. Cookies may be used to, among other things, allow
       automated log-in and may contain information such as a Login ID or other
       information about preferences or Internet use. Third party advertisers
       that we work with may also place cookies on browsers of users of our
       Service.
   • We also collect information about your movie preferences. For example,
       we may collect, among other things, information such as what movies you
       purchase tickets to or what theatres you attend. We may save information
       sent or posted to the Service. For example, we may save messages posted
       in our chat rooms or other message areas or feedback left for other users.
       We may collect correspondence, such as emails or letters, sent to us. We
       may collect user responses to online polls, ads, surveys, electronic
       newsletters and questionnaires.
Deletion of Information and Records
   • While www.cinepolisindia.com may track and store
       information, www.cinepolisindia.com shall not be obligated to do so and
       may delete any information and records, in whole or in part, at any time.
   • We use the demographic information to enhance your user experience by,
       among other things, delivering you content that is relevant to your
       interests. We may use the contact information you provide us to notify
       you of new services or special deals that we or our partners are offering,
       to distribute movie related information to you or to conduct surveys or
       other similar activities. When you register with us, you may choose to
       opt-out of receiving these notices or mailings
       from www.cinepolisindia.com at the time of registration.

   •  www.cinepolisindia.com does not sell or rent personal information about
      its customers to any third parties at this
      time. www.cinepolisindia.com does, however, perform statistical analyses
      of customer usage in order to measure interest in, and use of, the various
      parts of the Company's web site, and the Company may share that
      information with current and prospective advertisers, and other
      interested third parties. This information is aggregated data only (such as
      statistics), and contains no personally identifiable information
      whatsoever.
   •  www.cinepolisindia.com strives to protect the personally identifiable
      information of the users.
   •  www.cinepolisindia.com may disclose the personally identifiable
      information only on:
   •  expressed authorisation of the user to do so the provision of the
      requested service demands so requirements to comply with the
      governing law > opportunity to add value to the user
      However, www.cinepolisindia.com may share aggregated statistical
      information about the use of the www.cinepolisindia.com web site with
      partners and associates for the purpose of research and analysis. Even in
      these cases, www.cinepolisindia.com will strive to protect the individual
      users' personally identifiable information.
   •  Please note that www.cinepolisindia.com may sell, share or transfer
      personally identifiable information about its customers with any
      successor in interest (e.g. if the Company is sold to a third party).
      Additionally, in certain cases, www.cinepolisindia.com may be required to
      disclose your personally identifiable information when the law requires
      it, or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in
      connection with a criminal investigation, or civil or administrative
      authorities in connection with a pending civil case or administrative
      investigation.
   •  www.cinepolisindia.com users should also be aware that if they
      voluntarily disclose personal information in any chat areas or bulletin
      boards within the www.cinepolisindia.com web site, that information
      might be collected and disseminated by third-parties, and result in,
      among other things, unsolicited inquiries, messages, and offers from third
      parties. This third-party conduct is out of the control of the Company.
Security
   • www.cinepolisindia.com has implemented security measures to protect
      against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our
      control. We protect the secure areas of our Site with a firewall.
      Althoughwww.cinepolisindia.com has implemented adequate security
      measures, the site has contracted GlobalSign to provide an extra
      assurance of security. Although, the site is completely virus-free, the User
      is advised to employ virus scans for extra security,
      as www.cinepolisindia.com is not liable for any virus picked up at the
      time of transmission.

Choice/Opt-Out
    • www.cinepolisindia.com allows users the option to opt-out of receiving
        communications from us and our partners at registration. If you decide
        later to opt-out you can contact us by sending e-mail
        to support@cinepolisindia.com.
General Information
    • Please note that www.cinepolisindia.com tries its best to collect data from
        the most authentic source. However, at any
        stage, www.cinepolisindia.com is not liable for any loss, monetary or
        otherwise, resulting from the usage of their data.
Questions
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, you can email us
at support@cinepolis.com
